negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
Thank you for watching to the end.
We will bring you a new video in the next issue.
We will see you soon.
mmm
hmm
Hm
BUGGI BUGGI
Subscribe to our channel!
N
Hm
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
It's taking me a while to read the comments.
So I broke it up and said fog extra
's
Subscribe to our channel!
Hmmm...
Hmm...
Hm
mmm
Thank you for watching to the end.
We will bring you a new video in the next issue.
See you soon.
[Subscribe to our channel!
[Please subscribe to our channel!
Mmm
hmm
Hm
mmm
E great as ever
E great as everE great as ever
You know it's fun
You don't think about me
You talk too long
That's great.
Off you go
It's fine.
Good evening.
I'm Shunsuke Setoguchi, your administrator, and I'd like to welcome you to the Purple Kakkari, the newest addition to the Yuzukine family.
Now, just a few minutes ago...
I think it's been 8 minutes. I've just been invited to Amefurashi's show.
Thank you very much.
It was fun, it was fun, and it all happened so fast.
You talk a lot, Ameflasi.
You're so good at it. You're so funny.
I felt so comfortable letting him be the MC, even though it's his junior's show.
Yeah, don't think about it.
Think about it.
I was thinking about it when I spoke.
That's how relieved I was.
It was fun to relax and talk.
Amefurashi's always starts at 8:00 a.m., and for Yuko it's 9:00 a.m.
Yuko starts at 9:00.
Your friends are next door. Neighbors.
Neighbors, indeed.
They usually play until a little after 9:00.
After that, you'll be leaving.
We'll have you out by 9:00, and then we'll be ready for you.
We've already had about 1,000 customers.
Thank you very much.
Please tell us how Yuko's pictures will be distributed live.
Every Monday at 9:00 p.m., we are broadcasting live on YouTube's Orca channel.
From the well-known scraps of the real magazine game
Mr. Satoguchi and Yuko Oguuru, the orca, sometimes welcome guests and talk about various topics.
We talk about various topics with guests from time to time.
If you are watching this show, you can call them "roommates".
We call them "roommates".
Mr. Tahmin, a fan of Team Orca
And fans of today's guest, Amefurashi.
We will be calling them "roommates" during this time.
They haven't arrived yet, but I'm looking forward to seeing them.
I'm looking forward to it!
I wonder how it's going to be.
I was wondering how many times you've appeared on Yuko's Room.
She's been a guest quite a few times.
That's right.
Yes, she's been on a lot.
I have an image that Yuko comes here a lot.
That's right, that's right.
She's not here today.
And you, too, Mr. Tsutsumasa.
The four of us left at once.
Have we ever had four people come out at once?
Maybe not all four of us.
Each one?
Yes, 3 at the most.
Yes.
That's right.
Looking forward to it.
No, I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
But, Kojima-san, are you the favorite today?
We talked about it earlier.
Yes.
What? Why?
Sooooo...
Why don't you mention it?
Everyone likes it.
I'm sure everyone likes it.
You were talking about Kojima-san.
I like her. I like Hana-chan.
What do you like about her? There aren't any. I like cool girls.
I see. The other groups tend to have cool girls as their namesake.
Yeah, they're cool. They're definitely cool.
They take cool pictures on Instagram and Twitter.
I heard she hit 10,000 followers today.
Congratulations!
He's so cool, and yet he does impersonations every day.
You've got great skills, and you've done a lot of things.
And you know what else?
In your private photos, you probably like cute things like bags with ribbons on them.
I like bags with ribbons and cute things.
You like cool but cute things, too.
It's also a swamp point.
It's really good.
It's nice, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yeah. So, Moeka, right? Yes, what is it? It's Moeka, right?
No, it's not like that. She seemed very Moeka-chan. From the very first impression, you were like a Moeka-chan. What? Who is she? Moeka-chan.
I couldn't see her eyes. I couldn't see her eyes. Because you told me to decide my guess.
Was it because I was asked to decide on a favorite, or because I had already vaguely decided that it would be Moekachan if I had to decide?
I was told to think about it, so I wondered about it. What if I thought about it? I thought that he was the one I was most interested in.
Oh, you mean that I'm also looking at Eka-chan a lot? Why did I look up at an angle?
I was looking up at an angle during the delivery, like this. You mean you were looking up at her, right? Well, yes.
No, it's a real but extravagant problem. Lost. Luxurious hesitation. Also, you guys are always talking about yourselves.
I think that's also amazing. That's for sure. Everyone is amazing, of course.
Amazing. Well, before you come, let's do a shasha version of our usual corner. Yes!
This week's Sharts! Let's go!
Here is a recap of the week in the life of Team Shashe by Daikoku, a member of Team Shashe.In this corner, Team Shash member Daikoku himself looks back on the week in the life of Team Shash.
We have a lot more to talk about the Yuzuki festival, so what else did you have?
Let's see, yesterday, there was a re-release in Shibuya! Yesterday, there was a release party in Shibuya! Congratulations!
It was the day after Yuzuki's fair festival! Yes! We had a release party at night, and it was fun!
Was it fun? Yes! Is that all? What did you do?
We had a live performance and performed a song that we performed for the first time at Yuzuki's fair festival, so we performed that song for the first time at the re-release,
I see! You played it at Yuzuki's fair festival!
How was it?
What? How was it? Was it me?
The new song!
I don't know, the choreography was really good, and the choreography too, but Yuzuki's entrance?
Yuzuki's entrance was scary.
Shall I invite a guest?
The usual no.
I'm talking about Lilybees. I'm talking about Lilybees.
We did Trico!
The music video was released on the 3rd, and it's good.
Isn't it cute?
And easy to remember. Then let's invite them.
From AmeFlash, Aira-chan, Moeka-chan, and Yuzuki-chan!
Please take care of them for me!
Yay, yay!
I'm sorry I didn't get here earlier, but I'm afraid I've done a terrible thing.
I called you the way I always call you.
I mean me.
Can I really kick you out?
Whose room will it be?
Yuzuki's room.
The one that's not Yuzuki's room?
Please introduce yourself again.
My name is Moeka Suzuki.
I'm Moeka Suzuki.
I'm Aira. Pleased to meet you.
I am Mizuki Ichika. Pleased to meet you.
I'm glad to meet you.
I'm glad. It's been a while.
I know it's been a while for me too.
It's amazing how you decided to come, Amefura.
It's amazing.
Please explain a little. Ogura-san.
Amehura-chan performed at the second part of the Yuzuki's Room festival held the day before,
I'll tell you more about it afterwards, but I told her that I wanted her to come to Yuzuki's Room again,
The day after tomorrow? During the live performance, I asked him if he wanted to come to Yuzuki's Room again.
During the concert.
I thought about it, and I hadn't heard that a guest would be coming the day after tomorrow,
I thought that we might have a chance,
I looked at your face through the stage,
She looked like she wanted to check it out.
It was so light.
I thought, "Let's check it out.
I thought, "Let's ask her.
That's why it wasn't my cue.
I made a face like I was going to ask him.
And then, the day after tomorrow, Amefura-chan was decided.
That's great.
Thank you very much. So sudden.
Thank you for being a fan of Amehura-chan.
And then you also read Amehura's distribution as a set.
I'm so glad. Thank you very much.
But you know, I have my doubts, and I really wanted to leave Yuzuki's room.
I'm sorry, but you greeted me again after the hair festival,
Amefura's new CD, coffee?
Coffee.
I got it.
There was a message on it.
I was so happy to see you after a long time.
I was looking forward to seeing Amefura-san.
I was wondering if this will be on the program after this.
What?
It's a little hard to read, but it says "To Yuzu's parents.
Who?
Yuzu!
Can you see it? It's not for your room. It's for your parents.
This is impossible! You can't make a mistake like this!
I'm so sorry! It's my Yuzu.
Who?
Parents.
Yuzu-chan's parents.
Where is it?
Kojima wrote this.
You can't say he's not here.
Who wrote this?
I can forgive you now.
Thank you.
What kind of mistake is this?
I always write "heya" the other way around.
Why? It's not like that.
It can't be.
And when I wrote "he".
I realized that it was "Ya", not "He".
I should have filled it in with a heart.
But I thought since it was Mr. Setoguchi, he would understand.
Click!
You were blistered?
With a fistwith a fist
to the proper place
with a fist
It's also a Yashibushi.
It's a yashibushi.
That's why you're not a Yuzu fan, Setoguchi.
I wrote my own message because I wanted you to be my guess.
But then you'd write, "To my parents.
It's like solving a riddle.
Yes, a riddle.
No, I could have written it.
Actually, it was a riddle.
I don't know how you could have written it and said you wanted to leave.
When I got home, I thought...
I really wanted to get out.
But it's really because I always push Amershave for about 20 minutes.
I can't get out every time.
Also, you're on the radio.
I'm still doing it, but the daytime reading has changed.
I'd be very happy if you could come out.
I really wanted to.
Really?
I mean, you've done Hair Fest and Lilybug, and now today.
That's a lot of work.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's great.
Not at all.
Not at all?
I'm looking back at this week's Orca of the Week right now.
Can I look back at this week's Ameflas afterwards?
Yes, of course.
He said he was doing a re-release.
I'll tell you again what kind of re-leave.
On June 28th, I was a member of a reel called "Awaiting Bear".
Kenta Matsuguma.
Kenta Matsuguma will be releasing an EP with 4 songs.
To commemorate the release
In celebration of the release, I'm going on a free live tour with the EP.
We've already reached the end of the tour.
There are still a few places left to go.
The new songs are being revealed little by little.
Up until now, only one song has been revealed.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
At Yuzuki's Hair Festival, we premiered a song called
and we're going to play it at Lilybug.
We'll be performing that song at Lilybug as well.
The whole picture is becoming clearer little by little.
Did you hear the new song performed at the Hair Fest?
I heard it.
You heard it, didn't you?
It's so much fun!
Team Orca's live show always has some cool songs.
but there are also some really funny songs.
It's really fun!
I always have fun copying and pasting the songs!
I'm so happy!
You're telling me how happy I am!
You're saying that?
I really think so.
I see it. I see it.
I can hear it in my ears.
I also want you to copy the choreography with me.
Like the chorus.
And the chorus, and the tritoli.
The choreography is very simple, so I thought it would be fun to do it together.
I thought it would be fun if everyone could do it together.
So, I'm happy to announce it.
The music video has been released, so be sure to check it out.
Please listen to the other songs
and have a look at the dances.
I think it will be a lot of fun if you challenge to the live performance.
I think it will be a lot of fun!
Thank you very much.
Are there any more releives?
I think there is still a lot of fun to be had.
I'm sure there will be more re-leavings.
If you are in the area
If you are in the area, please come and visit us!
I'll be waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Anything else?
No, I'm done.
I was also preparing for Yuzuki's hair festival.
We'll talk about that later.
Okay.
Okay, Mr. Amefras.
How was your week?
Let's see...
Fine.
Check your schedule.
Uh, but...
A week ago.
Just a week ago
With Yuzuki.
We had a rehearsal.
That's right.
I smelled a little bitI smelled a little bit of it.
You told me about it the week before.
Rehearsal for the hair festival.
Rehearsal with Yuzuki-chan
Rehearsing with Yuzuki and Amefula...
I don't know, it's the first time.
What's it like?
You're a completely different member from usual, aren't you?
Yes, it is.
Do you feel any strange tension?
Oh, no, really.
We're so nervous.
I couldn't say anything.
It was really hard to say.
Rehearsal?
I don't know.
Let's be more aggressive.
We left the house with a lot of enthusiasm.
But now that we're in front of them...
I don't know what to say.
I was just trying to liven up the rehearsal.
That's right.
It was quite a reflective meeting.
I'm sure it was hard for you to say.
No, it wasn't.
You wore big sunglasses, didn't you?
I wish I wore big sunglasses.
Wearing furry poses.
How was it, Mr. Omura?
I had a blast.
It was a lot of fun.
Oh, wow.
Do I have to make it fun?
I wanted to have a good rehearsal.
I wanted to have fun with you.
Let's play Coco Coco while we talk.
Including the teacher.
The choreography was perfect.
We wound up way ahead of schedule.
We wound for over an hour.
I thought, "Yuzuki, you're good.
That's what seniors are for.
I was really impressed.
Did they send you the video first?
They were very kind.
I received the materials very politely.
But actually...
I really like Meguro.
I really like you.
Even if we go to festivals together...
I'll definitely change.
Even if I'm told to change at this time.
Even if I'm late, I'll definitely see you.
I'm glad.
Why not?
But you can apologize later.
Apologize later?
That's unacceptable.
You have to put your feelings first.
That's what he said.
Watch me.
That road...
I really especially like that song.
I actually choreographed it.
I was having a lot of fun with it.
The chorus is kind of perfect.
You looked like you were having fun
You were having so much fun performing.
It was really fun.
I could see Yuzuki-chan's butt fluttering
It was so cute!
It was so much fun!
And Setoguchi's surprise
It worked, didn't it?
I really wish you hadn't done that.
They suddenly changed it to rehearsal.
Turn it into a rehearsal.
Rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal.
Rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal
Rehearsal, rehearsal, rehearsal
rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal rehearsal
They put a microphone in my hand.
It's not like I'm talking.
Why go to all the trouble?
They gave me a microphone.
What's the point of having a microphone?
To say "What's the point of having a microphone?
To do it.
That was so funny.
It was so much fun.
At the beginning, there was a little bit
There was like a little dancing part at the beginning.
And they did a killer whale version of the
They did the choreography for the anthem.
We decided to bring Mr. Setoguchi to the rehearsal
We decided to bring Setoguchi-san to the rehearsal.
After the rehearsal, we said bye-bye in a cold way.
Bye bye!
I'm going home alone.
It's so funny.Very funny.
It's hard to say no when you can't say no.
I told you.
Because it's almost over.
I'll say no if it's too last minute
So when the music starts playing on the street.
I said, "I'm coming." I handed him the mic.
I think it's really good.
That's what I'm talking about.
We had already decided a week before the rehearsal.
But...
Mr. Setoguchi said he would come.
He said he would come.
But he did.
Of course he did.
He's an old man who does a lot of fiddling.
He was sandwiched in between everyone.
He's got his hands in his pockets, and he's got his hands in his pockets.
He's got his hands in his pockets.
Why do I have to get out of here?
You wouldn't like it if someone made a face.
I hate it so much.
Why do you hate me?
I didn't ask you.
No, you didn't.
Congratulations. I'm so happy for you.
How long has it been fun?
Did you have any other rehearsals?
Other than that,
Well, Mr. Ichikawa did a one-hop act by himself.
Mr. Ichikawa is doing a one-hop act by himself.
And you are the MC.
Yes, I was promoted to MC in April.
I was promoted to MC.
I was promoted to MC in April.
I was doing it.
It's amazing, really.
You know, it's really great, isn't it?
You're a good talker, Amefura-chan.
You are very active.
No, I don't think I told Moe-kun.
So this is it.
That's it.
Now, I don't think Moe-kun was in it.
Actively.
Was he not in it?
It was a confirmation that he wasn't in.
I didn't say anything about the house.
This is what I'm talking about, Setoguchi-san.
It's wonderful.
You seem to be smiling.
The balance is, wow.
I really appreciate it.
Everyone's type is totally different.
It's fun. It depends on the song. This girl stands out on this song, and this girl stands out on that song. It's like they are all over the place. That's why there is enough to know her in one live performance.
I am very happy that I have enough time to get to know them.
That makes me happy. It helps, doesn't it?
Hey, you did it.
I didn't do it. What's that Frisbee thing?
Try this.
You're good.
You're making fun of me.
Oh, no. You have a pout.
You call it a sulking mouth?
What's a pout?
It's cute.
He said, "Let's do it for the last time in your life.
Oh, that's right.
That's how we did it.
So they had decided on that, too.
And then there was Hana's appearance at the Folk Village by herself.
And Kojima-san was a special guest.
Like a secret guest.
I was in that position.
I don't know what I'm going to do if I'm the secret guest.
I'd be like, "Who's that?
Momoqlo-san is usually the secret guest.
Kojima said, "It's been a while since Momoqlo-san was a secret guest.
He said it was awkward, but he sang proudly.
It's funny because he's strong even here.
No, really.
Everyone is so strong.
We don't get complimented that often.
We don't have that when we are praised.
That's right, that's right.
I wonder if they are really happy.
Yuzuki, you keep going on and on for Momochan, don't you?
I am happy, but I don't know how to react.
I haven't received any compliments.
Yuzu-chan, who is so gruff, becomes very quiet.
Oh, she gets praised.
I feel like I'm getting smaller and smaller.
Is that so?
Please don't be so aggressive like you usually are.
You're being too aggressive.
It's not like that.
My hand movements are very gruff, but definitely not like this.
It's grueling.
That's not true.
I don't get that much praise.I don't get that much praise.
I get compliments.
That's a little fast.
We are the type that grows by being praised, but we don't get praised that much.
The people around us haven't noticed yet.
That means the people around us are no good.
That's because the people around us are no good.
Moeka is saying that quite teasingly.
I'll let them know, Ezuki.
Thank you very much. From a senior.
Amehara-chan is wonderful.
Even Daikoku-san grins when he gets praised.
He's a nitpicker.
He's the symbol of a person who grows from praise.
A symbolic person.
You are amazing, aren't you?
He was a symbol.
You're the kind of person who makes a happy face when praised.
I think that's good.
I'd like you to emulate it then. It's good to smile when you receive compliments.
It makes me grin.
Nita-nita.
I don't say "Nita.
You shouldn't say nita.
On Saturday, I had Yuzuki do my hair,
Yesterday, on Sunday, I had the opportunity to do a release for Shippo and Tachikawa Ritsunichi.
This is this releve?
Yes, it is.
Is this an album?
It is a mini-album.
There are a lot of cool songs on it.
It's true.
I'm glad.
How's the reception?
It's going great.
It's getting a lot of praise.
They're giving me a lot of compliments.
It's going great?
It's a great success.
If you don't listen to this, you're missing out, aren't you?
That's right.
You should do that much.
Since we had a photo-op time at this relieve,
Since we set up the photo shoot time at this event, it's been spreading on TikTok,
We've been able to get more customers through this release,
It's amazing.
Your recommendation.
Are you recommended?
They recommend me a lot.
That's great.
Maybe it's because I'm looking at it.
That's why I feel that this coffee is the most popular among the listeners.
It's great.
Yesterday, a lot of Yuzuki's fans came to the coffee shop.
I'm happy.
On the other hand, sometimes Ameura-chan's fans also come.
I'm glad.
Yesterday was the same.
I'm so happy.
There were fans of Setoguchi-san, too.
T-shirts.
Mr. Setoguchi's T-shirt and Yuzuki-chan's Happy T-shirt were there.
Oh my.
I think Daikoku-san's Happy T-shirt is good, but people wearing my T-shirt would immediately turn them into enemies.
I think they would be more pleased.
I'll keep that in mind.
Excuse me, Shu-Shu.
What is it?
On the one hand, we have a guest.
You have a guest on the other?
Daikoku-san, may I ask you to come in?
Isn't he the secret guest?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Dull guest.
Thank you for waiting.
Are you okay? Am I allowed to come out?
You're really out.
Can I get out? Here.
I didn't say I was coming, I was a guest.
It's just my schedule.
So you're wearing a mask because you're not wearing any makeup after the lesson?
Yes, that's right.
No face?
I can't show it.
You're going to show your face?
Why can't you take off the mask?
It's totally fine.
Yuzuki-chan said on LINE that she wanted to meet Yana-chan.
What's that? She didn't say anything about us.
Huh?
Daikoku, this is a problem.
Huh? That's not it.
Mr. Daikoku, the chair you wanted to call Kojima-san is missing. I'm sure.
Huh?
Someone should let him sit down.
Wai-wai-wai-wai.
We're waiting for a few people to come in.
To all my roommates who are watching, I'd like to say that Kojima-san is here too,
Please spread the word on Twitter with the hashtag "Yuzuki's Room" and this URL.Please spread the word on Twitter with the hashtag Yuzuki's Room and this URL.
Please spread the word.
Let's pursue this.
All of us together.
Did the three of you not have this?
No, they didn't. It was a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? Let's hear it.
We knew the delivery was coming, didn't we?
It was a given.
It was a given!
You told us in person after the hair base.
You guys are married on a dare.
Nana-chan couldn't see you, so I just said I wanted to see you.
No, no, no, test drive. Test drive.
I'm scared.
That's for sure. It's not much of a reason, is it?
Actually, at the time of the hair base, we were told that Hana-chan was our choice.
But Uchira-san dumped me without warning.
But everyone told me how much they liked her.
I know you are Nachan's guess, but I love you all.
I was saying that in a shoe and now it's a flower garden.
Wow.
By the way, Yuzuki-chan and I can DM each other on instagram, on line, or zero-hourly.
Yay.
I know you don't understand what I mean.
I haven't received any DMs. Yay.
Have you DMed her?
Nope.
LOL.
Hey. - Hey.
It's not good.
Daikoku-san does that kind of thing.
I love all four of you!
I don't trust you anymore.
About that.
You haven't shown it with your actions.
How about some persuasion?
It'd be creepy if I did.
It's just gross.
I'm sure it would be if I did.
So we'll never see Kojima-san.
If that's the case...
Of course you would.
I hate it so much.
There's so much DLC.
LOL!
I want to give it back! Characters! I'll give it back!
No! No!
You can't give it back!
LOL!
Ignore! Ignore!
Ignore Ki Dok!
No, no, no, I'm studying.
So, today we have all four of us!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Applause!
Surprisingly, this Yuzuki-chan
from the group
There have been three or a few people in a group
but not all of them!
I'm so happy!
It would be a problem if we were selected.
Everyone wants to be in the show.
Everyone wants to be in it?
I don't know.
It's arbitrary.
He's using me without permission.
That's right!
It's a good thing he's not here.
If you're coming, just tell me!
Shut up.
It's fine.
This way, please.
Mr. Amefura here, I've been asking you about your week.
Can you tell us about your private week?
This past week.
This is a real week.
There's been a lot going on.
I've had a lot going on.
I've been spending a lot of time with Amefura members.
I felt like I was spending time as usual
I felt like I was spending my time as usual.
Private
Wooooo!
Wooooooo!
You know, one of the characteristics of Amefura is...
The way you hit each member.
They're equally strong.
The last one is the worst.
They were all trying to make it a three-way.
Because you let me.
It's always the three of us.
That's what's so bad at the end.
This is bad.
When it's done, it'll be just like this.
I'm sorry, something just came up.
Congratulations!
It's okay that I wanted to shake your hand.It's okay if you wanted to shake hands with him.
The handshake was deliberate.
I could hear your voice.
I thought you were following my voice.
It's true, we came on our own.
You're the one who called us, right?
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-chan! That's not good.
We'll go on our own.
It's not good.
You're the one who was called.
Only the one who was called was different.
And that's okay.
It's thin and it's fine.
Long crap.
It's a long crap
Yooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Is it more than this week's series?
There is more!
Yes, what is it?
This week's Stop Lass PR!
This is a corner introducing a week in the life of Dai-chan, Batten Girl, and Tojinari and Ofusan, who are active locally within Stardust Planet, the group to which we belong.
Thank you to both of them for appearing in Yuzuki's Room. Thank you very much.
I was really touched by the kindness of the two groups, and I was so happy that they both performed in Yuzuki's room.
What do you think? What do you think? It's been a while, right?
Yes, it had been a while. I enjoyed watching from the side of the stage.
It was really nice. I felt he was so cool.
Daejeon is really good, too, and he is beautiful, beautiful, and cool.
I was able to see so many different types of Wajo-chan in such a short time, so I had a lot of fun myself. Thank you so much for your time.
Iginite Oak also performed in the second part of the show.
I would like to read a question from Ms. Karin Tachibana, the leader of Iginite Oak.
Please.
Yuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, my roommates, and everyone at Ameflash, Otsukare!
Good day!
I'm Karen Tachibana from Suddenly Far Away.
Thank you very much for Yuzuki's Hair Fest 2023!
Thank you very much.
I love Yuzuki-chan and Setoguchi-san, and I really like that wonderful atmosphere that flows at Yuzuki's Hair,
I really like Yuzuki and Setoguchi, and I really like that wonderful atmosphere that flows at Yuzuki Hair Festival, so it was very comfortable to be on stage with such a wonderful atmosphere.
I will always remember the time I spent with Yuzuki-chan, playing the fool with her. It was fun and Yuzuki-chan was too cute and an expert.
Yay!
Also, I was watching on the monitor, and the collaboration on the road was so amazing, I was watching with my mouth hanging open.
Eeeee!
As Setoguchi-san said, the last Enjoy Life was really a sparkling time that could be seen on sofas and so on.
Good.
I was also happy to receive a message from Yuzuki-chan. I will treasure it.
Once again, I thought Yuzuki's hair is the best and the strongest and I love it.
Thank you for the wonderful time.
Thank you for always being there for this week's position, Kanen.
I am secretly quite happy to have an excuse to talk with Yuzuki every week.
Please keep up the good work. See you soon.
Yes, thank you very much.
Kannen would like you to send me a picture of it after we are done, while I tell her thank you too,
I sent her a line and she sent me a message that I could scroll through, and I realized once again what a wonderful girl she really is.
I was able to collaborate with her on purpose on purpose,
All the kanen are really kind and I love them even more.
Thank you very much.
There is more.
What is it?
This week's night runner!
Yeah!
What is it?
This is one of our yuzuki's hair pure regulars.
This is Lulu's Runa's weekly recap corner.
Okay, I'll go a bit. Let's go.
Hello Yuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, everyone at Amefura, and my roommates.
Hello.
This is Night Luna this week.
The day before yesterday was the long awaited Yuzuki's Hair Fest 2023.
Thank you all so much for your support.
I'm so grateful just to be able to perform again this week,
I was so excited to be a member of Maiglo.
How was everyone's Maiglo?
It was great!
It was a lot of fun. Yuzuki-chan.
We were able to decide almost all the songs and costumes by ourselves,
We were able to decide almost all the songs and costumes by ourselves, and everything was decided easily without any fights.
Thank you, Yuzuki-chan, for everything.
Thanks to my roommate's immediate acceptance of our live performance,
I was so surprised that it was so exciting that I couldn't believe it was the first time for the three of us to perform together.
It was so much fun.
I was really happy to hear Yuzuki-chan say that it felt good to sing with just the three of us.
I hope we can perform at Room My Glo again.
Thank you for your cooperation, adults in all fields.
I leave it to others so much.
In the second part, I participated in the MC and karaoke contest as one of the pure regulars.
Even if the place changes, with Yuzuki-chan's personality and Setoguchi-san's fun,
I realized that even if the place changes, Yuzuki-chan's personality and Setoguchi's fun make it a homey and happy space as usual.
I love Yuzuki's hair festival, the most peaceful in the world.
Glasses Mark.
Thank you so much to all my roommates.
I also enjoyed selling the masks by hand.
Thank you so much.
And tomorrow we will be performing at Nighttime Land vol. 2.
Tickets are sold out, so please look forward to it.
Unfortunately, I won't be able to see the show on my rear tie since I have to stay up until the end of the night choreographing for Nighttime Land,
I will try my best to enjoy the lesson this time.
Thank you for your patience.
That's all for this week's night orna. Bybee.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
We did the Room Aiglo together and you were the MC for the second part.
He is one of the indispensable people for Yuzuki's hair, and I really enjoyed Room Aiglo.
He looked like he was having a great time.
Mr. Omori, you were really out there this time.
It was amazing, wasn't it? It was fun.
When we held Yuzuki's Hair Festival last year, we talked about how we wanted to do more collaborations,
That came to fruition, and I am very grateful for that.
I think you are very close to Mr. Night Owl, Mr. Kamebuchi.
Mabu.
I was with him just now at the rehearsal for Yakwangland.
Do you have a different side to you than the one you show to us?
That's it.
It's totally like that. Totally like that.
Totally the same.
So there's no difference at all? It's that feeling.
It's that feeling.
Even though we've been together for a long time, it's the strangest thing among us.
I can't grasp it. I see.
That's right. I see.
You're right. He asked me to hand over the mask of Mr. Zuishin.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate it too, Mr. Knighto, but it's so interesting to see the manager standing right next to you...
It's so funny to see the manager standing there with a very straight face.
I wish I had a straight face for my own talent selling Mr. Mizukami's masks.
If it were me, I'd be laughing.
I'd be biting my lip.
I'm just being serious.
That's kind of funny when you think about it calmly.
I don't think so.
It's too surreal.
Lots of male club sales department guy face masks.
Saying "thank you.
I was just wondering how you feel when you see the talent.
Thank you.
And there's more.
This week's Kojiwaflower!
Yay!
Something just arrived!
It just arrived?
What? When did you send it?
When?
A long time ago!
I'm so glad I came on such short notice today!
Yuzuki-chan is so cute.
She's so soothing!
Hey! I heard you're a Hana-supporter at Amefura.
I'm going to be a Yuzuki-chan guesser too!
Hi!
By the way, who do you want to have dinner with?
Who would you like to have dinner with the most?
Hana-chan!
Thank you!
My cell phone watch.
For Ira.
She's got that look on her face!
Ira!
He makes faces like that!
He's a head drinker!
Only Mr. Suzuki.
He's doing it halfway!
LOL!
Only Mr. Suzuki is doing something halfway!
So much!
I don't know what he's doing!
I have nothing to do!
I'm out of things to do!
I'll do it! I'm doing it!
I'm just doing something with the water spray!
LOL!
That was fun!
I'm so embarrassed!
When did you send it?
I just sent it!
What a surprise!
There's a notification here saying "Hana-chan"!
LOL!
I think Koshime-san is like that a lot.
I think you are like that a lot, aren't you?
You mean like a roller coaster on the earth?
LOL!
You're rolling around, right?
I'm rolling around.
Daikoku-sama, they just roll around on their own!
Most of the time!
He's got people on his own!
He's rolling around on his own!
Daikoku-sama, when they want to roll, they roll.
He's rolling over on his own!
He's rolling around on his own!
LOL!
I'm just relaxing a little bit.
I'm always impressed by the way you make up stories whenever you like.
Thank you for replying to all of my students' tweets!
Thank you very much!
Congratulations on reaching 10,000 people!
Applause!
10,000 visitors!
That's wonderful.
I'm glad you told us this week.I'm glad you told us this week.
I'm glad.
Yuki said she's thinking of dying.
No, no, no!
Grandma?
You lie too much!
Stop it! I'll use your thumb!
Look at that, I'll rub your thumb!
I'll rub your thumb!
That's not good.
How is it really?
It's a bit clearer around there, for sure.
What?
It's too heavy! It's heavy!
I thought you might want Yuki-chan starting today.
Oh, Hon-chan, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, Hon-chan!
What's this?
Then it's okay if Yasuyasuki-chan lines Honoka-chan
It's okay if I put that on the line.
Indeed.
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't do that, though.
Ha-ha-ha.
It's better not to do that.
I mean, it's private information.
It's all over the place.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's been going around a lot.
More than this week?
Thank you very much.
Let's see...
Yesterday, two days ago.
It was held on Saturday the 3rd.
Yuzuki no Yabesu 2023
I've received an e-mail from my roommate who attended the event.
I received an e-mail from one of my roommates with her impressions of the event.
Thank you very much!
Of course, I'd like to take a look back at the feedback e-mails.
I'll look back on it.
I'll give it to Daikoku-san.
Yuzuki can read them.
I may not be able to introduce all of them.
I may not be able to due to time constraints.
I'll try my best.
Room name
Stromina
Ms. Stromina
Where would you like to be?
Stromina
Stromina.
Mr. Daikoku, Mr. Setoguchi, and everyone at AmeFlash
Good evening.
I had a great time at Yuzuki's Hair Fest the other day!
I was having so much fun that my brain was wobbling!
I find myself going to this event every year.
I've been going to Hair Fest every year, and this year, I was able to enjoy the free and wild atmosphere that is unique to Hair Fest.
This year, too, I was able to enjoy it to my heart's content!
As usual, all the groups were great!
but this time I was especially impressed by AmeFlash!
I was so happy!
It's been a long time since I've seen Ameflash, and all the songs were so cool!
The sound and lighting at JEP Kamitake were so good that I was really excited!
I was so excited!
I was especially excited to hear "Fly Out".
I thought it was cool when I heard it before, but
but this time it was so good that I couldn't understand it anymore.
My brain juices were flowing like a river!
The way Hana-chan jumped as hard as she could on any of the songs and landed straight on her feet
I was shaken to my heart's content to see such a beautiful dance when I saw the strength of her body.
It's been a long time since I heard the orca's "Horizon," but I'm still numb to it.
It reminded me of the hachamecha pasik of a scalp tip, and it was very moving.
Fabo was so much more fun than I could tolerate.
My memory is a little hazy.
The headbangs in the auditorium were beautifully aligned
It was exhilarating!
One of the joys of Hairfest is that
is that I'm the last one to go all out and win the best.
Orcas at Hairfest are my favorite!
Hairfest has become a big part of my annual fun!
Looking forward to next year's event.
I'm looking forward to next year's event, and I'm going to work out for a while in the aftermath of this year's event.
Thank you Mr. Goto for a great Hairfest!
P.S.! P.S.!
You don't look so thick-mouthed
Aoi Rirua-chan, a member who doesn't appear on the front page
I can't wait for the day she comes out!
I can't wait for it!
Thank you very much!
I see you're very satisfied with my work.
That makes me very happy.
I'm glad you enjoy it.
Mr. Ameura, you're really...
The atmosphere at Zep Shinjuku is
really fits the atmosphere of Zep Shinjuku.
suits the atmosphere of Zep Shinjuku very well.
The live broadcast was
very much.It's amazing.
I'm glad.
Really cool.
grin
That's cool.
You should be proud of one of them.
Um...
What do you think?
Also...
I mean...
The outfit looks really good on you.
Really?
They all look great on you.
They look good.
Matching outfits.
Matching outfits
I thought it was really cool.
It's so cool.
I'm glad you're here.
A lot of people are here.
Mr. Ameura's fans, too.
I want to do a lot.
Please do.
Room name Ar-chan
Yuzuki-chan
Setoguchi
Aear-chan
Yuzuki-chan
Moeka-chan
Hana-chan
Good evening.
Thank you for your hard work on Yuzuki's hair festival.
I'm embarrassed to say
I didn't know Hana-chan very well.
the other day at the Ayaka Nation.
I was curious about Hana-chan
I was inexperienced enough to follow her on various social networking sites.
It's true.
The performance hid a line from the rest of the group
I was so glued to the stage that I forgot to shake my pennite
I was glued to the stage.
Hana-chan's earphone in her right ear
seemed to have come off.
Hana-chan continued to smile and sing with an impressive volume of voice.
I felt her professionalism.
Thank you very much.
And a little different from the hair festival
Setoguchi-san's birthday festival could also do something
I'm sure others will touch on the contents, so
I won't say much, but
It was a very, very satisfying birthday festival!
I'm relieved to know that Mr. Setoguchi turned 38 years old without any problems.
I'm relieved.
In order to participate in the special event
I bought a copy of "Escape from Puroland Alone
I bought it.
I'd like to play on my day off.
Last but not least
Thank you all for your hard work!
We are looking forward to seeing you again next year at Yuzuki's Hair Fest.
We look forward to seeing you again next year!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much!
I was so surprised at the amount of work that went into the birthday party.
I was surprised too!
I think I might be the same age as your mother.
Mr. Setoguchi.
I'm a little shocked.
What?
Can you stop me?
How old did you say you were?
Thirty-eight.
My mom will be 39 this year.
December.
What? You're the same age!
You and I are not the same age.
My dad...
That's not true.
Oh, my God.
Seriously?
You mean like a dad?
I mean, I feel like a dad.
What?
That's amazing.
It's not amazing.
I feel love.
I'm feeling love.
You scared the shit out of me.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said so much.
I'm sorry, but I'm 80% sure.
You're a cock!
Oh, really?
I'm so sorry.
Not at all.
You're not?
Just like your father.Like your father.
Kanji. How do you look up?
How do you look up?
Oh, yeah.
That's amazing.
That's a little scary to think about.
That's exactly the kind of thing I want to hear.
Is Aya's mother young?
She's young.
She's beautiful.
She's even brasher than Aya.
She's so vivacious!
Brilliant!
I want to see it.
Biri!
Oh, I want to see!
You're not Pikachu, mom!
You're a big brat, aren't you?
You're such a brat!
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, my God!
I'm shocked.
I can't tell you.
I'll go on.
We'll continue with the room name, Neroaru.
Good evening, Yuzuki, Setoguchi-san, and everyone at Amefura.
Good evening.
I'm Yuzuki's Hairy Beth, and I'm pleased to be able to attend both parts of the event.
The Tokaido Shinkansen was closed in the morning on the day of the show.
I was worried that it would be after 2:00 p.m. when some parts of the show starts at the earliest.
But since the opening time has been delayed by 30 minutes...
I couldn't dwell on the fact that there were people who couldn't come by any means.
I waited for the bullet train with a determined determination to get there.
As a result, I had to enter the venue about 20 minutes after the opening of the first part of the show.
But I was able to get same-day tickets for the first and second parts of the show, as well as for Setoguchi-san's birthday party.
It was a very enjoyable day!
The highlight for me was Yuzuki's collaboration with Michi.
deliberate bruising expert!
The highlight for me was the backless time during the MC's performance!
Yuzuki-chan seemed to be having so much fun!
It made me happy too!
I can feel the love and youth of the audience!
Yuzuki's Hair Bess, please keep up the good work!
Doubun
Excuse me.
I'm sorry for my rambling.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
The way to the song for the collaboration is to point to Daikoku?
Yes, I've always wanted to do it.
Isn't it cute, the choreography
He wants to try it.
I'm so happy.
I want to do "I'm curious, I'm curious, I'm curious, I'm curious" too.
You've been doing it for a long time, haven't you?
You collaborated with almost all the groups this time?
The second part is a collaboration.
You've been doing it for a long time.
How do you manage to do all that?
It's a lot of energy.
But it was a lot of fun.
And I got to meet a lot of my guesses.
I'm totally fine.
It was fine.
It was great!
He talked a lot to Tao Nakamura and the others.
He stayed with us until right before we left.
It was fun.
I see.
It would have been the opposite without it.
When did you hear about this? Daikoku-san wants to collaborate?
Since when?
But that's exactly when you told me you were going to perform at Yuzuki's fair festival, and you said you were going to collaborate.
I was really looking forward to it.
It's not often that we collaborate with our seniors.
It's not often that we get to collaborate with our seniors, so we were really looking forward to it.
So it was a lot of fun. I was really happy, really.
I asked you three earlier, how did you like it? What did you think of Daikoku-san's performance of "Bi-ha"?
Oh, it was really great.
I remember it perfectly.
You said it.
Why don't you say the same thing?
I didn't know him.
You weren't there.
You're being too hard on him.
I'm so depressed.
Pick a place where you don't think he'd say it.
Let's go home.
Ah-ha-mo!
I'm sorry, but I was wondering if you could say something else.
No, something a little different.
Well...
I came here in casual clothes.
But I came home in my lesson clothes.
I don't know why.
I don't know if that's a good image.
I wonder why.
I wanted to ask you here.
I wondered why.I wondered why.
It's such a hassle to change.
You came in plain clothes.
So I was embarrassed at first because I was alone.
But on the way back, you and the manager...
We met there.
I thought it'd be less scary.
I see.
I'm glad we broke up.
It's all sorted out.
It was a bit of a hassle getting home.
You're so cute.
You guys don't go home in your lesson clothes, do you?
I'm totally going home.
Yuzu is so bad.
Basically, I go home in everyone's lesson clothes, but...
But I can still go home like this.
I'm going home in a fashionable way.
Ichikan is wearing pink pants and a light blue T-shirt.
Shoes are always the same, like thick-soled sandals or heels.
Or heels.
To match her plain clothes.
And match it with her lesson clothes.
I've only met someone on the side of the road once in my life, so I thought it'd be okay.
I'm usually the only person who's ever met someone on the side of the road once in their life, so I thought it'd be okay.
I'm not wearing twin-tails in front of my hair.
That's fine.
I'm not going to say "boo-boo," but it's definitely nice to have that kind of sunny outfit on your clothes.
I'm not hiding.
So if you think I'm with you now, I'll be with you from now on.
It's better not to be with her.
But I just remembered something.
Yunuki made a mistake in the lesson at the rehearsal and was late.
I was late.
What? Why didn't you tell me that yourself?
Well, Hana had rehearsed before that rehearsal.
On a different lesson
I was just watching at random
I thought we were going to have a lesson there.
I see.
It was just a flow.
Then, there was a person who had nothing to do with the lesson who was in front of the lesson.
I had never seen him before.
I wondered if he would come to the rehearsal for the hair festival.
I see.
No, there were people who would never be involved here.
I wondered why, so I went downstairs.
I went downstairs and heard the voices of people who looked like they were going to perform at Night Land.
I thought, "Wait, this is definitely not the same thing," and then I saw that they were in a completely different lesson room.
What's the matter, were you in a hurry to get there?
I was in a hurry, but I figured it couldn't be helped, so I decided to take a cab.
That's where I got a cab.
I almost made it. You almost made it?
Why is that bad? I was just in time.
Why is it wrong to be on time?
I was just in time.
And I'm so glad I did.
But then the cab driver went down the wrong street.
It's a dead end.
Oh, I'm done, I can't make it.
Here's my excuse.
I'm late.
Always the cab driver with Yu...
He always takes the wrong way.
Yes.
He really does make a lot of mistakes.
That's right.
You're lying, right?
It's not that common, is it?
That's what I thought.
You thought so?
I'm sure it's not true.
Can you stop making me feel like you're on my side?
Can we all stop being on Kojima's side?
All of you.
They're probably just saying, "No, we're not.
He's trying to show Moeka how good he is.
Moeka.
That's how you feel.
Sorry about that, Moehana.
I'm sorry, but I don't see where that was a good point.
She's blaming the others.
Are you just taking the blame?
He's trying to show Mr. Suzuki how good he is.
It's so fucking lame.
I'm cold.
I'll text you, right?
Okay, then.
I'm off!
My pen name is Haru-chan, Aira-chan, and my favorite friend, Chi-Chi.
Yuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, and everyone at AmeFlash, good evening!
I've been going to Hair Fest every year because I'm a Tough Min past Harumin. And I'm a big fan of AmeFlash.
I've been to a couple of shows by Noinari and his wife, so the second part of this year's Hairfest was great, to say the least!
I hope to see more orcas and Ameflash in the future!
Aira, are you okay with your butt?
I'm fine.
I fell down.
You fell?
Yes, I did.
It's a very lively song called "Turn Twister.It's a fast-paced song called "Turn Twister".
I was dancing to the tune, and I got a little bit giggly.
I fell down with a lot of noise.
It was so embarrassing.
I really wanted to throw up.
Really?
The truth is...
I mean, the solo, the downhill, it was right on time.
I'm embarrassed to admit that I gave up halfway through.
I couldn't stand it.
I can't stand it if I don't say it.
But then came the lyric, "If you fall down, just get up.
So I thought, "This is delicious.
I'm glad I fell down. The people in front of me were worried.
I know, right? I was watching him afterwards.
I was just watching the show, and after a few songs, I thought I'd just go over there and watch.
And then I fell, and it was like...
I was like, "What's wrong? What's wrong?
I'm sorry for worrying you.
I'm fine.
But... you have this image of perfection, Ayata.
So when you fall down...
But it's fine from our point of view.
No? She's far from perfect.
I wonder how many times a day she falls... she falls a lot.
I stumbled three times today, and I felt it.
So I think everyone was worried about me after they saw me do it. I think everyone was worried.
From our point of view, we felt as if they were doing it again.
No, the three of you were trying to be professional and to follow through.
I was so worried about them.
It's been a while since I've been on the Samurai site.
Everyone's like this.
So of course the fans are watching.
They're looking at it.
My eyes just popped.
Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you okay? I have to tell him.
There was a staff member in the back taking a video of us.
It was so funny.
Look at that.
Are you okay?
While you're worrying about me, I'm not even trying to touch Ira.
I just did it like this.
All the time.
It's a half-assed move.
I love that video. I've seen it so many times.
He's so cute.
So cute.
Let's go this way.
This is Ms. Pirika Yume, room name. Thank you for the Yuzuki hair weight.
I would like to say that it was great, but due to the typhoon, I had to work and couldn't make it to the venue.
My personal dream was to see Lumaiglo's first love cider. I have been a fan of Hello Project since before I met Mr. Daikoku, and I have had the opportunity to talk about songs with him several times at benefit events as a fellow Hallo Pro fan.
About 5 years ago, you may not remember, I wrote a letter to Mr. Daikoku, telling him that I would like to listen to Yuzuki-chan sing Hatsukoi Cider someday.
I am disappointed that I missed the perfect opportunity to do so this time, but I saw on Twitter and other media that the three of them were wonderful, and I applauded them for singing Hatsukoi Cider, a song that is said to require great vocal ability.
I was very happy and proud of the fact that they were able to do it, not that they did it or did not do it. Thank you very much.
How was it? How was it? I told you that it was surprisingly smooth to decide on the songs.
Yes, it did. We submitted our requests, and if they said they didn't like the song, we would choose another song.
I'm sorry to hear that you were disappointed that you didn't get to see it, because Hatsukoi Cider is legendary among Halo-Chlo fans.
What do you think? Two years ago, it was just you and Mai Haruma, and this time, Roo, you have adults in the group.
I hope there will be more members.
That means you want more and more people to join, right?
Yes.
For example, the person who is here today is one of the members of Megurashi.
If they were to join Lung Maigros, they would stop at just one person.
I already know that.
I don't know, it's a matter of balance.
First of all, there's that condition.
Conditions
I have to be a nerd.
And being a nerd.
And also, there's not a lot of fabric.
Uh...
I think we've all cleared the "not too much cloth" part.
It's not too much cloth, is it?
Not so many.
I don't have much skill.
I'm pretty much all over the place.
Not Yuzu, then.
I have a condition.
No, but...
I'm cleared as an otaku.
And by the way, the other three may not clear otaku.
Uh-oh.
But really...
I mean...
If I had to choose seriously.
Yuzu might be the one with the right tension.
Really?
She's definitely not like that.
Why? Daikoku-san says she's the leader.
You mean in front of the loompan?
I don't know...
It's not like Muff's Angel.
I'd say he's rather cute up front.
Well, he talks a lot.
I have an image of him... cute.
I have an image of him as cute, and Rumpin is kind of quietly giggling.
I don't know... when it comes to geeks, I think there are a lot of gung-ho types.
I don't know, I'm not the type of person who simply cheers behind your back, but I'm the type of person who cheers for wartime, and since the three of us are otaku who cheer for wartime, I think that the gung-ho type would be a good fit for us, so please do!
If you were to join us, is there any song you would like to sing? I want to sing!
By the way, what is the name of your group? If it's "Lumike", it's "Lumike".By the way, what is the name of the group? If it's Lumicron, it's Lumicron Key.
key
lmicro key
The key
I don't have an image of the most keys.
I liked the yuzu.
Key
Le micro key
key
Isn't key a kiss key?
Kanji characters change too.
Of its own accord.
You're right.
Whenever you do it, it's like "halo pro".
It's true, but...
Just one favorite song.
Any part is fine.
Anything at all.
I have a song I want to say something about.
Youth Subliminal
Wow!
I know, right?
You must join!
The leader approved it.
That's pretty easy.
We all like it.
I see.
Who do you like?
I like Maika.
Ikarin.
Yes, I love Ikarin.
I'm in.
Ki joins?
A tree joined.
Isn't that the only thing that's kind of special about it?
It's a tree? It's a tree.
Wait! I'm sorry about that.
A tree.
Louis Malmy Brockie.
I'm like a tree.
If you could do it backwards, you'd want to sing, wouldn't you?
Yes, I'd like to sing it.
That's a good one.
Oh, man.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I hope you'll watch this whole thing.
I did it! Let's do it!
We're not going to change the name again?
Yes.
We should give up.
Let's do this.
Here we go.
Room name Hina-chan.
Yuuzuki-chan, Setoguchi-san, Mefura-chan.
Good evening.
Personally, I especially liked the deliberately and intentionally expert, the day, and the ultra super miracle super belly power ball.
I was so happy to see Yuzukichan perform Expert and Sun on purpose on purpose, and everyone looked so happy and happy.
Yuzuki-chan was so cute when she was being hit by Kaaya's favorite girl. I've always wanted to do the power ball as a vocal performance, but I didn't think I'd be able to do it so soon, so I was really excited.
I was so excited to be able to do it so early.
I also had a great time receiving power and becoming a water god and seeing a live tree man.
Thank you so much!
I think there were many fans of Ameflaes who came to see the show.
I wonder if they understood the tree man part of the show?
I'm really worried about it, but I don't understand the power of the water god, do you?
I don't know.
The viewers are really confused, aren't they?
I think I laughed the hardest at the tree man.
The mysterious fight between the three of them.
The three of them had a mysterious fight.
It's got a hole in it.
They're worth a lot of money.
Really?
Yes, they are.
It's very popular, isn't it?
Yeah, everybody loves it.
I'm glad.
The choreography is catchy and it's easy to listen to, so we get a lot of likes.
Do you have a favorite Amefura-chan song, Setoguchi?
You performed a lot of songs from here this time.
I thought it was really cool.
I never listened to the CD.
I didn't listen to the CD, but I heard the song on the subscriber's site.
It's so cool!
I'm so happy!
I can play it all the time and listen to it.
It's like it raises my spirits.
It's the type of music that both men and women like.
It's like a club event.
I've never done that before.
It definitely goes well with this kind of thing.
It's definitely a good fit.
We really want to do it.
I think it's really good.I think it's really good.
That's why I think ZEPP Shinjuku is a little bit
The perspective of the live show is a bit...
It's like that.
So I'm really happy to hear from you.
I'm glad.
I really want you to do it.
We've got a lot of new songs in the set.
We've got a lot of new songs in there, and we've got a lot of feedback from the audience.
We've gotten a lot of feedback that it was a lot of fun.
I heard that on Twitter.
It's going to go up, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
I'm sure they don't know how to call.
Everyone's already adapting so quickly.
We had a lot of fun.
And speaking of collaboration, I also got to meet with Mr. Tohoku.
I'm an expert now that I know you.
That was more like a collaboration.
I mean, we got a lot of lessons from them.
You know, they made it possible for us to take pictures only then, right?
I saw a lot of it on Twitter and other places.
Daikoku-san only made this face the whole time.
I see it all the time.
He's shot in all of them.
That's right.
It wasn't supposed to be like that.
Wasn't supposed to be like that?
Yeah, that's what this project was originally about.
Not like that.
It was supposed to be a collaboration.
It was a collaboration.
If you'd done it like that...
I'm going to be tossed around again.
I'd get carried away again.
And then the nine of us would roll him around with a wave of our hands.
You're on TikTok, aren't you?
Yes, I didn't know.
You did, didn't you?
Can you dance?
I do.
You guys are amazing.
Mr. Kitise, he called me Mr. Setogushi.
I said, "What's going on?
He said, "Can I take a TikTok with you?
He said, "Yes.
He looked so scared.
I said no.
Then, I don't know if it was the manager or a staff member.
I don't know if it was the manager or a staff member, but they went with a woman.
I said, "You can't have an old man like that on your account.
I'm just saying that.
I'm serious.
It's a rights issue, isn't it?
How can it be?
We're freelancers.
We are?
We're freesos, too.
We're freeso.
We're a freeso association.
A freesaw society?
Never heard of it.
We're a freesaw group.
We'll be posting a lot of these on the site.
Were you able to meet a lot of people? The other performers.
We were all in the same dressing room.
It was a big dressing room.
Yous are having a lot of fun watching all the kids from different groups.
I'm not calling you.
That was great.
I thought it was great.
I didn't.
That's what you thought from your mom's point of view.
No, it wasn't.
I went to the Stabler Institute.
Alone?
What were you doing alone?
Boo Boo is so nice, I'm scared.
Mr. Suzuki, you don't seem very friendly.
I couldn't go. I'm so nervous... even though he's an alien.
I'm so nervous.
I'm tempted to just say, "Thank you very much.
I just want to get to know this guy.
I'd like to get to know him.
When I went to Thailand with the Tohoku group...
I chatted with Mie.
I thought we could become friends.
But the next time we meet...
But the next time I met her, we had no relationship.
Mie is shy, too.
That's true.
That's why I want to get to know her better.
But once you get to know each other... persuasion is the third virtue.
Oh, really? Really?
Look at this.
Wow!
Wow! It's Otachi!
I got this for you.
Oh, wow!
They're from Yuki's support staff.
If you had told me you liked me back then...You know, back then, if you had told me you liked me...
I didn't have a choice.
No, I was gonna go all eco-friendly on you.
If you'd said that.
Right?
You're right.
For Setoguchi's sake, get to know Miyu better.
But I like your shyness.
All schools lend a hand!
The whole school lends a hand.
She likes that, too.
I like that, too.
I'm glad you found your own guess, Mr. Setoguchi.
I've been telling you to make a guess.
I see.
Your life is shining.
You've worked so hard to become a school-wide geek.
If you say so...
That's great!
I'm so glad you wrote me a nerd letter.
Yo!
It's not a "Yo!
It's not a "Yo!" It's a "Yo!
Anytime, Mr. Family, it's basically just a random letter.
Yo!
I'd be happy if you'd give me a really serious look.
Really?
Thank you for letting me be a good guy.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Anniversary of your guess
The anniversary when you met your guess.
Yes, that's right.
We've received a lot of e-mails from you.
We have a corner for this.
I'd like to ask you to let us know about it again next week.
I will keep you posted.
Thank you very much.
Since Mr. Amero's guest appeared on the show today
I would like to share her story with you.
I'd like to have it with you.
Is it okay if I go to the corner?
What's the title of the corner?
I don't know.
You're free to choose.
Any title.
Let's focus on Amehura.
Let's focus on it!
Let's focus.
I want to.
It's not enough.
You've come all this way.
That's why you're here.
That's why
We all kept our mouths shut.
There's a lot of tipping information.
A lot? A lot?
Worst, worst, worst.
From all sides.
Oh, no!
I've been working with people from all walks of life.
That sounds like a lot of people. I don't like it.
So, who's giving us this information?
Why, who?
It's coming from someone.
Someone is anonymous.
I don't know.
Well, tell us.
If you could secretly make eye contact
If you make eye contact...
I'll make the exchange.
I see.
Uh...
I wonder if it's from someone.
Shall we do it?
Do you have any information that you can share with us?
If anyone.
I'd be happy to process your face and voice.
I'd be happy to process it for you.
We'd be happy to do that for you.
Anybody?
I'll give you some privacy.
Okay, I'm not sure if I should tell you.
I'm sorry, I'm Eilers.
I don't know who this is. I'm Eilers.
I'm Mr. Eiler, and you're the one with the information about Mr. Eiler?
No, I'm Mr. Eiler. - You're Mr. Eiler?
"Eiler" is a bad name, but I'm gonna go ahead and say it.
Can we not do that? It kind of ruins the whole setup.
If you insist on calling yourself Mr. Eiler, then I guess you are Mr. Eiler.
Do you have any information for me?
Well, I have information about Mr. Suzuki's intake.
Mr. Suzuki gave it to me.
Ha-ha-ha.
You said you don't have many friends.
Yes, you did.
But you said you wanted to make friends.But you just said you wanted to make it for your friend.
And yet...
I was acting pretty strange, and I was in the same school as the students at the school.
The students seemed a little uncomfortable going to the catering and wondered if they could take pictures.
So I told them I'd go with them.
And then suddenly Monica and I were there with all the other students, and they were like, "Oh, no, we're not going.
But Moeka went back to the school and said she wanted to eat lunch by herself.
I think that's the reason why I can't make friends.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
I got some information from a guy named Irace.
What about it? Is it true? If you admit it, you should admit it.
If it's not true, you can say it's not true.
It's true.
Wait a minute.
There was a group of students at Staply. Yuzu and I went to talk to them.
Oh, yeah?
With who?
With Yuzu.
Isla? Isla?
With Ira.
With someone named Ira.
I want to go get it.
I thought we could go together.
I've been really wanting to eat lunch.
I'm a little nervous.
I wanted to slip out again.
You invited yourself?
What do you mean?
Just say bye-bye and eat your lunch.
Poor girl.
That must have been a little rough on him. I don't know.
I don't know. Did you throw it away? Did you throw it away?
I don't know.
It's a yuzu, right?
Did you throw it away?
It was an unbelievable thing to do, to say the least.
He said he'd go with her, but she didn't want to go.
But he just left on his own.
If I said I wanted to go home to eat my lunch...
You can't say that, can you? I can't deny it.
But I want to be friends with you.
I don't understand.
Maybe it's a little difficult.
Why don't you help him?
I'm the same way. I understand.
I totally understand.
I want a friend.
But it's hard for me to talk about it, so I run away to be alone.
I can't stand the atmosphere.
I see.
I think about that when I greet people at Amefurashi.
Is that what you think?
Situations like this.
This is it.
He's happy.
She's happy.
You are?
Really?
In a room you can't see.
She's so excited.
Yes, I know what you mean.
I'm sure, you know, the four of us are always half a step behind.
It's like someone's a little bit hidden around here.
That's right.
Is there something else? Somebody's information.
I'd love to hear it.
Is there anyone who can tell me what's going on?
Anyone?
I don't think that kind of information is very hard to find.
I can see it.
I still talk to them with my face.
No one's touched it.
Did anyone take the initiative?
No one.
No, no, no.
It's okay. I'm sticking to you now.
There's no one in the bathtub.
I'll give you some privacy.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, uh...
Excuse me. Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Excuse me. Um...
You're the one with the information, right?
Yes, I was just, uh...
I was just...
To be continued...
I'm tentatively scheduled for two months.
Thank you.
I'm a little more nervous.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
The Stabla student who just came in?
What's going on? You said it hurt.
Yes, yes, yes.
The stabla students...
Yes, yes.
Backstage.In the dressing room
I didn't have my smiley badge.
So we were in the hallway.
And, um... we were...
We were in the hallway.
I told him to sit down.
And we let them go inside.
And there was this big table.
And there were some chairs.
He said, "Sit here.
And we all sat down.
sat down, and at some point
"Sit here.
We let them out.
And the stabla students
said, "Thank you," but
But there was one person who didn't win because he was worried.
I wondered about that.
I wondered if there was more to the story.
Still going on? There was more to that story?
There was a continuation? Is it still going on?
I've been eating my lunch while saying "No, no, no." I've been eating my lunch all day.
I was just wondering what's going on... so I had a curry combi.
Oh, I see.
Since he's here today, I'd like to ask him if this is true or not.
I'd like to ask her if it's true or not, but maybe it's the way she says it.
It's true.
Wait a minute, what do you mean?
I was eating lunch.
You were eating lunch, weren't you, Suzu?
Yes, I was.
We were short on chairs for all of our students.
We had to bring in chairs from various places.
We brought chairs from various places so that everyone could sit down.
We had several chairs at each table.
You can sit while you eat.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Lord.
Did he say, "Come here"?
I said, "Come here, come here.
But did you watch them eat the whole time? He said, "Come here, come here.
I thought maybe you could show her a chair or something.
I'd like it if he moved. He was eating.
You don't want to move when you're eating? She wants to concentrate.
She can't eat standing up. She wants to get along.
That won't solve anything. But if I say I want to get along with you...
Is that so? I don't think I want to get along.
I thought I'd end up sitting next to one of the research students.
I thought it would be someone sitting next to Momi, but then I wondered why this girl invited Hana to sit next to her.
She made Hana sit on the balun, so she's sandwiched between the cushions.
Why did you tell that to Hoshino-san? Anyone is fine. Just the stabla student.
But I want to get to know them.
Put the flowers down.
You didn't talk after all?
Well, in the end...
It's great. With Hana and the others there, the research students are more interested in talking.
I thought she wanted to get to know the other one, too, so she'd talk to him.
And he just kept saying "huh".
That's all he said.
I'm scared.
I'm getting scared.
I see.
You're so clumsy.
You're not good at broaching the subject on your own?
No, but...
I'll do my best.
But I don't think so.
But you are.
She's happy at school.
You told her that?
But I wanted to ask him about it.
I asked her myself.
That's right.
She didn't want to expand on it.
I'm having fun at school.
Like, "You heard that, right?
I'm trying my best, but...
But from there...
I totally understand.
It's true that many people have a certain image of you.
I totally get it.
I see.
She's a little mysterious.
I'd be happy to hear the other side of the story.
If anyone has any information.
At least one more.
Or information about someone else.
Yes, of course.
At least one more.
It's better to reveal the truth.
That's right.
I see.
Excuse me.
Do you have any information?
Yes, I do.
Is that so?
Whose information is this?
May I have some information about Kojima-san?
Yes, I do.
I went to the store you were going out with the other day.I was in a restaurant the other day.
I had the opportunity to perform at a restaurant that I have a relationship with.
There were a lot of goodies brought in.
I think the performers probably said it best.
I've been going to the gift shop for years
I was taking a lot of sweets.
Shut up!
Shut up, you ogre!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I thought there was something after this.
Wait a minute.
From...
The information is so naive.
I'm embarrassing myself.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Embarrassing.
That kind of backhandedness.
I see.
Embarrassing.
It's embarrassing to be told this information.
It's a dare.
Kojima-san's here.
Is this true?
Is it not true?
May I have the information?
It's true.
I don't care.
It's no damage.
No damage.
You said so yourself.
I'd recommend it.
How much did you say?
How much do you have in terms of body weight?
Noooooooo!
Did he say he couldn't do this at all?
He said he couldn't do it at all.
Like this? Seriously?
It's so impossible!
How do you carry it all the way backstage?
He's so heavy.
It's too heavy.
What are you carrying?
It's so heavy.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mr. Spachu...
That's crazy.
Of course it is.
Hold that there.
You must have been surprised.
I didn't know they brought this.
What did you say? Kojima-san.
Amazing!
I said, "Wow!" You guys!
He said it's amazing.
He told me.
That's right.
Didn't you warn him later? Mr. Kojima...
He did.
Oh my God!
He gave it to you!
Did you share it with him?
He brought you some?
Yes, I did.
I went and made it myself.
I'm sorry, I just...
I couldn't.
I'm just trying to get to know you.
Don't make it into a story.
I'm telling you the truth.
Yes, it's true.
You too, Daikoku.
I want to make lots of friends.
Where are you? Mr. Suzuki.
Moeka?
But...
Moeka...
We happened to see the same play.
It was quite a while ago.
And when I got out of the ticket gate
I thought it was you, Moeka, so I talked to her.
I felt like I was talking to a stranger.
What?
Did you do that?
Seriously?
I'm fine.
It's just that the next one is next door or something.
It's pretty normal.
Thank you for your time.
I'm sorry.
So you're not Ietsuki anymore?
I wasn't expecting you.
Is that what this is about?
Remember when Daikoku was next to you?
I don't know.
But it was a long time ago.
You were busy with your lunch, weren't you?You were busy with your lunch, weren't you?
That's right.
You were eating your lunch, weren't you?
At the ticket gate.
You used the turnstiles.
But you know...
We're having a meeting about Ame-Franc.
Whenever something like this happens...
I'll tell you what to remember.
I'm going to tell you what to keep in mind.
The staff or the manager explained it to us, but on the day of the meeting
But on the day of the meeting
I didn't listen to it.
There are so many cases.
It's really common.
I'm sure I heard it right at the time.
It really suited me too well.
I'm like...
It really suits you.
Oh, I see.
Daikoku-san, you already knew that, didn't you?
I thought maybe you didn't notice.
On the contrary, I thought I was Mayaka and talked to her.
But I thought you were the wrong person.
Well, then...
On the contrary.
That's how much she didn't know me.
You understand, don't you?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
So I wondered what was going on.
I thought, "What's going on?
I was like, "What's going on?
It was a different person. But it's the same, you know.
I didn't know he was on stage.
I didn't know he was on stage, so I thought it was a mini.
So maybe I got the wrong guy.
I thought so, and then I saw you next to me, and I thought for sure it was Moeka.
I'm scared... I'm scared...
I don't know what's going on here.
I don't remember any of the five of us.
No, but I'm sure it was Yuzuki.
Moeka, Yuzuko and Hana were there when I went to see Yuzuki.
That's right. I was next to Moeka.
Yuzuko and Hana were in the play.
That's right.
I'm sure you two noticed.
But I didn't see you at the ticket gate. I'd like to meet and greet you at that stage.
Are you beautiful then?
I remember.
You remember that?
Stay with Hou.
Yes, yes, I remember.
How many hours before you went up that hill?
What?
We've met.
It's getting scary.
I'm turning into a piggyback.
I'm meeting you.
Tell me what to talk about next time.
One more thing.
Remember when I was with you?
What? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You met before that?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't know you were at work.
And I tried to talk to him like this, but...
What?
Do you remember talking to me?
Do you remember when someone talked to you?
At the ticket gate?
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
That's funny.
I didn't think they'd give us this kind of information.
I didn't expect it.
I thought Moeka was pretty solid.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was interesting.
Yuzu was the only one who didn't seem to like Amegra-chan.
Please stop it!
Suddenly I feel like I'm going to explode!
I'm the only one who looks like she's about to explode.
I thought it was like that.
That's what it's like.
I can't stop wrapping it with Mobler.
What's that?
It's like it's all of a sudden on the other side.
I guess we're all like that now.
I love that.
Thank you.
That's so cool.
You've given me some good information.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'd like to make an announcement.
If there is any news from Amegra, please let us know.
Yes, we are actually in the middle of a releve...
There are only two more sessions left.
The next one is next week, June 11th.The next meeting is next week, June 11
Aeon Mall
It will be held at Tokoriki
Aichi, Japan.
And the last day is June 24th
at Raraport Toyosu.
We're hoping to reach our goal of 500 people.
We're working very hard to achieve our goal of 500 people.
I would be very happy if you could invite your friends to come and see us.
If you are interested, please invite your friends to come and see us.
Please come and see us!
And on July 9, I'll be doing a one-man show, Biosign 2023!
Oh!
It's a two-part show, and I'll be playing as SoulDar for the first part, and then I'll be playing for the second part.
Thank you very much.
But both parts are completely different, so there are only a few tickets left for the second part, which will be held at Shinjuku Lenny.
We have a few tickets left for the second part, so please come to Shinjuku Lenny.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Let's go, Mr. Shachi!
Yes, Killer Whale is also in the re-league.
We have many more venues, so please come and visit us if you can find one near you.
And on the same day, July 9, I'll be having a one-man show in Nagoya titled "Shachi Diner Shachi".
One part of the show will be my birthday party and the second part will be produced by all the members, so please come and join us!
I can't!
I would be very happy if you could do your best with a smile and a niko niko (happy smile).
On July 22nd, I will be giving a big one-man live performance called "Orca-sama" at Nagoya Castle.
This is a big event that we have been doing every year since I was president of this team.
This time it will be held at Nagoya Castle, the place where we made our debut!
Every year we have been able to enjoy a lot of fun and frolic at the live concert, but this time it will be at Nagoya Castle, so we will be able to enjoy various feelings.
But this time, we will be performing at Nagoya Castle, so we will have a lot of mixed feelings.
I think you will be able to see the orca like you have never seen before.
If you have seen orcas at any point in the past 11 to 12 years, this is the concert you should definitely come and see.
If you haven't seen us live yet, we would like you to know about us.
We are looking forward to seeing you there!
I love it!
Thank you very much.
That's all.
I'd like to let you know from the scraps.
Let's have this person introduce you.
Let's have Mr. Mizukami from the scrap sales department tell us.
Please do so.
Scrappers
Don't you like it?
Scrap
I'm starting to hate you.
Please don't break it.
I'm Mr. Mizukami from the scrap sales department.
Yes, ma'am.
And, um...
Yes...
Are you kidding me?
Please inform us seriously.
Yes, sir.
To the scrap sales department.
Scrap Sales Department, Labratiol and his Escape.
I'll introduce them as...
Yes, sir
This year, we are coming to this kind of Conan's Escape again!
Visuals of Conan and Hyval wanting to play an active role will be on display in the exhibit room
And it's about to be sold out!
You mean it is already sold out?
Yes, sir.
The visual of this activity...
Since it was presented to the institute
I'm going to confront the case in your letter.
Shut up.
What's the big deal?
You've got to be serious.
It's so funny.
It's an important speech.
Yes, it is.
I've come so far that I can't hear a word you're saying.
That's right.
Yes, please.
In this shooting recipe.
That's all for this video!
Look forward to the next one!
Oh, I don't want to talk anymore.
I've decided to keep my mouth shut.
I've been working on various sections this time.
What's the main storyline this time?
Yes, it's going to be...
It's more about the father. It's through images. It's been a while.
That's right.
We'll be showing you some of the parts of the Dad's Money Out series. We will be asking you in the future about your response to this one.
Yes, thank you.
Oh, was that the mayor? I love Conan.
I love it.
You can come if you want.
I'd love to come.
You'll be inside the world of Conan.
That's amazing.
You said you're wearing a lab coat.
That's right.
Isn't it great?Isn't it great?
This movie was good, too? Did you see it?
I saw it twice.
Oh, it's good.
It was great.
It's one of the best, isn't it?
That was great.
Wow, I want to go.
Please come.
Yes, I'll be there.
I have one more announcement.
Mr. Mizukami, please.
The end of the film series will be this month in March!
Another Image and Love ad has finally been released!
Yes, it's Image again.
The film series will celebrate its 10 millionth viewer in March next year.
The series will be held at the end of this month
The biggest gal-pal game of 2023!
The theme will be a summer festival!
How many people participated in the game?
1 person? Up to 10 people can participate at the same time.
Thanks to the urgent ranked
You can solve all the gals
You can solve all the gals and get in besides the horror.
Is this someone's message?
Is this the installer?
Yes, this is it.
May is... August 26, 2023.
August 27, 2023.
Yes, the 5th.
And at the venue, right?
We will also have a scrap gallery on the 24th.
Yes, sir.
From now until now, the new series of products will be
The fastest sales of live-action new items
Um, and other weirdly anticipated items will also be held
Yes, Beef Skate Rattle Boy start
You can enter 20 minutes before the event, so
so that you can enter before and help mark
We hope you will be able to use it.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
We are going from here in the previous session.
Yes, please.
Please help us.
We'll be doing five shows on Saturday and Sunday.
If one comes.
I hope you will come. Thank you very much.
Mr. Mizukami is also aiming to be a great person, so please support us all. Please support us.
Thank you very much, Ms. Mizukami. Thank you very much.
And, may I introduce Yuzuki's thumbnail?
Yes, I do. We are currently holding a project to recruit thumbnails.
We received the invitation ticket from Echo. Here it is.
Wow! This is the 202nd time. This is the last one. Yuzuki's hair base open rehearsal.
Yes.
The first time we did it. Setoguchi-san is the main thumbnail.
Ah, thank you.
Also, Eiko's different illustration touch is cute.
Cute.
It's something to enjoin a life of flames.
Yes, it is. You taught me about life on fire, but pretend.
From Daikoku-sensei.
Here is a thumbnail of it.
Thank you very much.
You are very good at it, aren't you?
You are also wearing an online T-shirt, aren't you?
Thank you very much.
It is in the overview section.
You can reach us at rumattscrapmagazine.com.
Any times are fine.
Please send us the thumbnail. Best regards.
So, there you have it, Mr. Daikoku.
It went by so fast,
I think it turned out to be a very interesting episode.
It was interesting.
It was really interesting.
Onodera-chan's delivery was a lot of fun, too.
We had fun, too.
I'm from the stream too.
They also came to Yuzuki's room.
I asked her to come to Yuzuki's room, but I didn't think it would happen so soon.
I didn't think it would come true so soon.
Really.
Thank you for your light footwork.
No, no, it's my pleasure.
It's a staple lunch hookah.
I really think so.
It's hard to decide, isn't it?
Really?
Surprisingly, you know, it's not well known,
Yuzuki's room, if you drop Yuzuki a line and
Yuzuki's room is available if you call her and say you want to leave.
Surprisingly, it was not well known among the staff.
Among the staff.
So, please contact me anytime.
Then, let me represent you,
Suzuki.
Please let me know.
Just when Suzuki thought he wanted to leave.
I'm just going to end it right away.
But the person I'm sending the DM to,But the person I'm sending the DM to,
I don't know whose kid it is.
I think it might be this one.
It's too dangerous.
What should I do?
I'd like to have her appear in the predecessor's term,
I would like to be represented.
Sometimes I want to make an announcement.
Other times, too.
Even when I'm not busy.
I think I'm busy,
I happen to be on YouTube,
If you happen to be on YouTube and have some free time, we would love to hear from you.
I would appreciate it.
I'd be happy to do it any day of the week or the same day.
Is that okay?
I'm sure you'll be fine, Osawa-chan.
I'll have Suzuki contact you.
I'm counting on you. You must do it.
Will you do it?
What do you think?
I'd like you to do it.
Please do.
I'll be waiting for you.
That was interesting.
How was it? Did you enjoy it?
It was really fun. I felt that Yuzuki-chan and Mr. Setoguchi got to know each other better day by day,
We were able to talk with them in a very relaxed manner,
We were able to relax and talk with them, but after listening to messages from Karen and Rumpin, we felt like we had to go lower, like we were messing with them.
Not at all. I feel that.
Karen has her own qualities, and Rumpan has Rumpan's qualities.
Karen alone is such a naughty girl.
Please stop it!
That's the problem I've been having lately.
But we're all a little too eager to be teased.
Really?
Then let's do it!
Be moderately popular.
But I'm glad we're getting to know each other.
Please keep up the good work.
I'm looking forward to it.
Since we are here, may I ask the five of you to close the meeting?
I don't care how you say bye-bye to each other.
I don't care how you want to say it.
Okay.
Thank you very much for watching this week's show.
Thank you very much.
Seino
See you next week! Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Good night. See you next week!
Thank you very much.
Watch the next video!
mmm
hmm
Hm
mmm
[Subscribe to our channel!
Subscribe to our channel!
[ED]